{
    "questions": [
 
        {
            "flashCardFront": "おはよう",
            "flashCardBack": "Good morning",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Good morning", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good afternoon", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "How are you?", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "おはようございます",
            "flashCardBack": "Good morning (Polite)",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Good morning (Polite)", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good afternoon", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "こんにちは",
            "flashCardBack": "Good afternoon",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Good afternoon", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good morning", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you for the meal (before)", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "こんばんは",
            "flashCardBack": "Good evening",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Good evening", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Goodbye", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "さようなら",
            "flashCardBack": "Goodbye",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Goodbye", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Nice to meet you", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "おやすみ（なさい）",
            "flashCardBack": "Goodnight",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Goodnight", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you for the meal (after)", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good morning", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "ありがとう",
            "flashCardBack": "Thank you",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Thank you", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good afternoon", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "I'll go & come back", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "ありがとうございます",
            "flashCardBack": "Thank you (Polite)",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Thank you (Polite)", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good morning", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Sorry; Excuse me", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "すみません",
            "flashCardBack": "Sorry; Excuse me",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Sorry; Excuse me", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you for the meal (after)", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "How are you?", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "いいえ",
            "flashCardBack": "No; not at all",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "No; not at all", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you (Polite)", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Goodbye", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "いってきます",
            "flashCardBack": "I'll go & come back",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "I'll go & come back", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Sorry; Excuse me", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good evening", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "いってらっしゃい",
            "flashCardBack": "Please go & come back",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Please go & come back", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good afternoon", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "I'll go & come back", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "ただいま",
            "flashCardBack": "I'm home",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "I'm home", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Please go & come back", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "おかえり（なさい）",
            "flashCardBack": "Welcome home",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Welcome home", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "I'm home", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "How are you?", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "いただきます",
            "flashCardBack": "Thank you for the meal (before)",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Thank you for the meal (before)", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you for the meal (after)", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Goodnight", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "ごちそうさま（でした）",
            "flashCardBack": "Thank you for the meal (after)",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Thank you for the meal (after)", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you for the meal (before)", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Nice to meet you", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "はじめまして",
            "flashCardBack": "How are you?",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "How are you?", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Good afternoon", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Thank you (Polite)", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "よろしくおねがいします",
            "flashCardBack": "Nice to meet you",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Translate",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "Nice to meet you", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "I'm home", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "Goodbye", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        }
 
    ] 
}